Steve: Hi, Jenny.
What a surprise!
Jenny: Hi, Steve!
Steve: How are you?
You’re looking great.
Jenny: Thanks. I’m well.
How about you?
Steve: I’m OK.
Hey, it’s starting to rain.
Would you like a coffee?
Jenny: Oh, thanks, Steve, but I have a meeting in an hour.
Steve: Oh, come on Jenny.
I’d like to talk to you.
Jenny: OK. A quick coffee.
Steve: Jenny, I’d like to ask you something.
Jenny: Yes?
Steve: There’s an exhibition of Picasso at the MOMA next week.
I know you love Picasso.
Would you like to come with me?
Jenny: Listen, Steve.
I’m really busy at work at the moment.
Next week isn’t a good week for me.
Steve: Sure. No problem.
Maybe we can meet one evening,
when you have more time and… have dinner or see a show?
Jenny: Listen, Steve.
I don’t think it’s a good idea.
But thanks.
Oh, look at the time!
I need to go.
Let’s ask for the check.